+353 83 124 6901 arturcmjr@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/arturcmjr github.com/arturcmjr

ARTUR JUNIOR

Summary

Full stack developer with experience in all stages of the development cycle for web projects. Practical knowledge of numerous modern technologies. Focused on front-end lately yet can work perfectly with back-end. Visualizes the whole thing from the user's perspective to come up with ideas and solutions for possible problems.

Skill Highlights

Soft Skills	Hard Skills
	i iui u skiiis

- Fast learner
- Self-starter
- Creative
- Critical thinking

- Angular
- .NET
- DevOps
- SQL

Experience

Game Developer - 05/2017 to 07/2018

Roundstars, Brasilia, Brazil

- Worked on developing single-player and multiplayer games. Coding core mechanism, search algorithms and bots Als. Programming, making interfaces and arts for those games.
- Wrote clean C# code for games on Unity Engine.
- Helped with a REST API for a social media for games with PHP and MySQL.

Web Designer - 12/2018 to 10/2020

ADRA Brasil, Brasilia, Brazil

Worked with a little bit of everything. I helped automating daily tasks with VBA and SQL, made
art for fundraising campaigns, developed a system with Laravel and Vue to help with hot meals
distribution for Venezuelan refugees.

Full Stack Developer - 10/2020 to 09/2022

Adven.Tech, Remote, Brazil

- Worked developing web apps such as a stock management, event, e-commerce and other systems on client demand. I also helped to migrate legacy systems to modern technologies.
- Written clean and scalable code for the back and front end. Worked with popular technologies such as Angular, React, .NET, C#, SQL and others.

Education

- Graduation on Game Development 2018, IESB, Brasília, Brazil.
- Post-graduation at System Analysis and Development 2022, Descomplica, Remote.
- Post-graduation at Mobile Development 2022, Descomplica, Remote.